The app automatically keeps track of your Repertoire: the list of tunes you know well. Let's learn how this works, and how you can use your Repertoire.
Every tune has a Comfort Level — how well you know it. Let's change the Comfort Level for this tune.
You can set the Comfort Level yourself. For this tune, let's choose "I know this one." Your Repertoire is all of the tunes "I know this one" or higher.
When we save this change, the tune will be added to our Repertoire. Let's go see.
You can filter the library to show just the tunes in your Repertoire. We see the tune we added earlier. This is good when your mind goes blank in a jam.
You can also look at your Repertoire during a pratice. Here's how. First let's start a new practice session.
"Go straight to" lets you see different views into your library. Let's tap "Repertoire".
And there it is. The tune is listed in the Repertoire, because we said we know it. There's a second way to get tunes added to the Repertoire. Let's check it out. We'll go back to the practice session.
If you rate a "Got It" three times in a row, the Comfort Level will go up automatically, so it will get added to the Repertoire. Like in this example with "Whisky Before Breakfast," let's say this is the third time. This time, when we've got it...
...and we go back to the Repertoire, it is there now! Now when you look back, you can see that this is a tune you know pretty well.